Well, you know...
The fact that I cried... keep it a secret, okay?
You definitely... won't tell anyone, okay?
Okay, Hinata.
It's our secret, then.
Thanks.
And also...
From now on, Instead of calling me Hinata, you can call me Ibuki.
Eh?
But... why?
Well...
That's...
Ibuki-chan!
Ui!
I knew you would have gone to the viewing platform!
Geez, it's mean of you to not tell me!
Everyone was worried-
Oh?
Eh?
Kazu-kun...
Why are you...
futari de mita haruka kanata no ryuusei
二人で見た遥か彼方の流星
The distant shooting star we saw.
haato no puromisu
ハートのプロミス
Believe in our promise. As much as you'd call it true love.
ai to ieru hodo shinjite
愛と言えるほど信じて
You stop, as if you'd do that...
Hoshizora e
Kakaru
Hashi
Chihiro Fansubs Presents
Hoshizora e
Kakaru
Hashi
kaze ni yureru kami osaeru you ni
風に揺れる髪　抑えるように
...to keep your hair from fluttering in the wind.
kimi wa tomadoi
君は戸惑い
I painted my cheeks red...
koi no hajimari to kidukanai de hoo wo akakushita
恋の始まりと気づかないで 頬を赤くした
...so I wouldn't notice that I had fallen in love.
ikusen no hikari ryoute de hora
幾千の光両手でほら
You have myriads of light rays in your hand.
hoshi wo sukutte
星をすくって
Come on and save that star.
hitori no yoru demo waraeru you ni
一人の夜でも　笑えるように
So you can smile even on a night when you're alone.
omoi de wo hanabi ni shite
想い出の花火にして
Turn them into fireworks of your memories.
kimi to boku no uta ni nare
君と僕の唄になれ
And let them become a song for us.
saa ten made todoke kono kimochi
さぁ天まで届けこの気持ち
Let the heavens know...
kokoro wo gyutto tsunagou
心をぎゅっト繋ごう
...about our love that connects us firmly.
yowakutatte iin da boku no te de
弱くたっていいんだ僕の手で
It's okay if you're weak.
sono yume wo hippatte iku
その夢をひっぱっていく
I'll grab your hand and realise your dream.
kakehashi ni na itai yo
架け橋になりたいよ
I want to become your only bridge.
kimi hitori no kirari niji ni naru deshou
君一人のキラリ虹になるでしょう
I'm sure we will be shining forever...
boku ni kimi wo eien ni
僕に君を永遠に
...brightly like a rainbow.
Episode 8
Jabs are (Blank)
Thanks for your help!
Is our delivery the last?
Yeah.
Then, do you want to come in and get a cold drink?
I have to get home quickly and study.
I see.
Hina is looking forward to the new semester.
Yeah.
I wonder if it's going to be hard...
Yup yup...
That's true, isn't it?
Hmm, yup...
Well, I'm totally free...
Eh?! The beach?
I'll go! I'll definitely go!
There's nothing to do during summer vacation, and I'm so bored!
Then, I'll see you next Wednesday.
I'll contact you again once we're done sorting out the details.
Yup, okay!
Also, help me get Ibuki to come,
since we're all going to the beach.
Ah?
Hey, Ui?
What's wrong?
Oh, erm...
All right.
Okay, I'll tell Ibuki-chan.
Oh, Madoka-chan does volunteer work at a library during summer holidays?
Yes.
I read books to the children, or do picture book shows.
She doesn't just do that, she also reads out her own works,
which seem pretty popular with the little kids!
Oh, I see.
It's not all that popular...
Well, I've enjoyed writing stories ever since I was young,
and when I told those stories to the children,
everyone seemed so happy, so...
It's amazing to be able to make children happy using your own stories.
So, are you shocked?
It's nothing for you to boast about, is it?
What did you say?!
My friend's pride is my pride!
What's wrong with boasting about it?
By the way, Sakai-senpai, you're studying even now?
Exam students have their battles in the summer.
I'm sorry for having kind of forced you to come along.
It's important to take a breather once in a while.
And...
What should I be sorry about?!
This is a good chance.
Once I'm alone together with Hoshino,
I'll apologise properly for that incident.
It's the sea!
Sea, sea, sea!
Hey!
Do your warm-up exercises before you get into the water!
Geez, they're so childish.
And in comparison...
This side is so mature.
Y-Yeah...
Come on, Koumoto-senpai, quickly, quickly!
I'm not mentally prepared yet!
Koumoto-senpai, why are you hiding?
Your figure is good enough for you to show off!
Ah!
Eh?
I didn't get thrown.
Well, Kazuma-san was the one who invited me here...
This, of course, shows that we're friends.
Besides, there is no need to throw you when you touch me...
If there's t-too much contact, I can't promise you anything...
What do you mean, "Too much contact"?
Madoka-chan, let me do that.
Ah, okay...
There you go!
Thank you very much...
Then, let's go!
Okay!
Take that!
Take that, that, and that!
Stop!
Counter-attack!
Take this!
Eh?
Let me engrave the power of the water gun into your memory!
Seems like you guys are making a sand castle.
Ah, Onii-chan.
Ibuki, thanks for staying with Ayumu, but...
...is it fine with you not to swim?
Eh?!
It's nothing much, is it?
There's no rule stating that you have to
swim when you come to the beach, is there?
Well, Onii-chan, Ibuki-san says she was just like me and can't-
Ayumu-kun!
Can't swim?
But Ibuki, weren't you able to move along the river by emitting oil bubbles from your butt?
There's no need to remember those kinds of details!
Could you at least get back at me
with your fist instead of your foot...
Being unable to swim isn't a bad thing.
But it's good to work hard and learn to do things you couldn't before.
Come and learn to swim with me.
Yes, if you please!
Then, Hinata can learn from Hoshino.
Eh?
I probably can't do it...
Eh?!
That's right. Keep it up.
Yeah, that's the way.
Now put your face down.
Put my face down where?
Well, wouldn't that be the sea?
O-Okay.
That's right.
You can do it if you want to, can't you?
Hey, are you o-
I thought I was going to die!
Well, you would if you held your breath for too long...
Then say that earlier!
I can't pull that kind of thing off!
Also, I would be able to swim if I could pull that off!
Ah, Ui-chan, having a break?
I was thirsty, so I was thinking of eating some shaved ice.
Tsumugi-san, do you know where Kazu-kun is?
We were playing together, but he suddenly disappeared...
If it's Kazuma-san, he's over there.
Seems like he's teaching Ibuki-chan how to swim.
Kazu-kun is... teaching Ibuki-chan?
That's right, that's right!
Keep it up!
What's the matter, Ui-chan?
Eh?
I-It's nothing!
I'll go buy some shaved ice!
Ui-chan...
Hoshizora e Kakaru Hashi
Hey, Madoka-chan.
Where's Tsumugi-san?
Tsumugi-san said she had something to do and asked me to look after the belongings.
Oh man, I even bought her some shaved ice.
Madoka-chan, do you want this?
Eh?
Is it okay?
Yup!
Are you okay?
It's because you ate it so quickly...
I know, but it doesn't feel like I'm
eating shaved ice if I don't do it like this.
Ah, that was delicious.
I'm alone together with Nakatsugawa-senpai.
There might not be another chance like this.
If I want to know, I have to ask now.
Erm, Nakatsugawa-senpai.
What is it?
I don't know if it's right to ask you this though...
Go ahead.
Then, I'll ask.
What do you think of Kazuma-san?
W-What do you mean?
Well, that's...
Whether you l-like him or not...
Eh?!
I don't dislike him really,
and because I don't dislike him, I kinda like him...
Ah, but although I do like him, this is like a love for a brother...
Ah! That's right!
It's the same as liking your own big brother!
Big brother?
Madoka-chan, why do you ask?
That's because...!
How should I put it...
That's...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Ah!
A watermelon!
I thought everyone would like to do watermelon splitting,
so I bought it from a seaside store!
Then, I'll go call everyone over!
Ah...
Eh, if I remember correctly, I, Minamikokubaru Daigo,
began watermelon splitting a long time ago,
when I was still a small child-
It's too long!
The watermelon will become all slushy!
That's right, that's right!
All right, already!
Then...
Let the watermelon splitting begin!
I'm ready!
You really can't see anything through that, can you?
I can't see through it.
I can't see anything.
Then you can't tell whose chest this is, can you?
It's rather flat...
Could it be Ibuki?
I told you to get back at me with your fists...
Here I come.
Right, right!
Too far right!
Not there! Do a half-turn!
It's here, huh?
No, it's here!
Take this!
Ibuki! You can definitely see through that!
Here I go!
It's here!
To be able to tell where the watermelon is just by smelling. As expected!
That's amazing, Ui-tch!
Well, this is kind of different from watermelon splitting...
Okay!
We're going to play beach volleyball, so let's split up into teams!
Where's Sakai-senpai and Ayumu?
I don't know about Sakai-senpai, but since Ayumu looked tired,
Tsumugi-san asked him to rest.
Then isn't Ayumu alone with Tsumugi-san under the parasol?
Then could they possibly be...
Ayumu-kun.
Could you help me rub the oil on my back?
O-Okay.
You're good, Ayumu-kun.
You're very good at this.
That's right, rub it all the way into my skin.
That's good.
I'm done.
Now, it's Ayumu-kun's turn.
I'll make you thoroughly sticky with my breasts.
Ah!
...doing things like that-
Not possible!
This is pretty painful, you know.
Tsumugi-san?
What is it?
Tsumugi-san, do you have something you want to buy?
Eh?
I was wondering why you worked part-time at Yorozuya Inn.
Ah.
To me, working at Yorozuya Inn is like a rehearsal.
A rehearsal?
I was thinking about working at Yorozuya Inn when I grow up.
Why do you think that is?
Erm...
Is it because you like Yorozuya Inn?
That's partly correct.
However, what I love isn't just Yorozuya Inn, but the whole of Yamabiko Town.
The beautiful river, the clear blue sky, and the crop fields.
And above all that, the warm connections between everyone.
Or maybe I think a little too highly of it?
I think so too.
Thank you.
The inn is a place to receive people from other places, isn't it?
If I do my best and manage to please the people there,
wouldn't it make them feel like coming back to my beloved Yamabiko Town?
And through that, I want to make
lots of people love Yamabiko Town.
"This place is great!"
"When you are happy, or when you are down, this place always receives you with warmth and kindness!"
I'd like to achieve that.
That sounds a lot like Onii-chan.
Eh?
I'm like Kazuma-san?
Ah, not that.
The fact that Yamabiko Town is always there for you,
and always treats you kindly, sounds a lot like Onii-chan.
Ah.
But I've spent so long causing trouble for Onii-chan...
That's wrong, Ayumu-kun.
Kazuma-san has been working so hard for you in order to let you smile.
However, if you make such a sad face because of that,
Kazuma-san would definitely be disheartened.
If you're grateful to Kazuma-san,
instead of thinking about how you've been causing him trouble,
try smiling for his efforts in order to make him smile.
Wouldn't that be good?
Make Onii-chan smile...
I understand.
I don't know what I can achieve, but I will try my best!
Oh...
It's cute...
Sakai-senpai!
So this is where you went.
Everyone's already changed, and getting ready to head back.
So, let's go.
Everyone's waiting.
I'm alone with Hoshino now.
It's a good chance to apologise to him.
Hoshino!
What is it?
Well...
I'm sorry.
It's fine!
There's no need to apologise for something like this.
Anyway, let's go!
That's not... what I meant...
We had fun today, didn't we?
We sure played a lot!
I've got to take a bath once I get home.
Hey, Ibuki-chan.
Hmm?
When did Kazu-kun start calling you Ibuki?
Eh?!
Ah, well... I wonder when it started?
I don't remember...
But, why do you ask?
Well, there's no particular reason!
I was just curious...
I see.
Yup.
That's all.
Really.
chotto matte yo
ちょっと待ってよ
Wait a second!
yume no tsuzuki kana
夢の続きかな
Why are you continuing with your daydreams!
shigyou beru no gofun mae da (u—n)
始業ベルの五分前だ(うーん)
You were studying just five minutes ago
mezamashi mo nidone
目覚ましも二度寝
Your alarm clock already rang twice
ja shouganai ne
じゃ、しょうがないね
So it can't be helped
yada seifuku no manma nechattetanda demo rakkii
やだっ制服のまんま寝ちゃってたんだ... でもラッキー?
Oh no! I slept with my uniform on, but how lucky!
hai tenshon de ikou konna tokya!
ハイテンションでいこう こんな時ゃ!
It's time to go with high tension!
nandemo kandemo DORAMA ja arumaishi
何でもかんでもドラマじゃあるまいし
Everything isn't like in drama's
umakuiku monka tte omotteta (fu—n)
うまくいくもんかって思ってた(ふーん)
I thought it would turn out smoothly
shokupan wo kajiri
食パンをかじり
Nibbling on white bread
kado wo magaru
角を曲がる
Make the corner curve
to hatto! masaka ne
とハッと...! まさかね
See! It's impossible!
sukippu sukippu
スキップスキップ
Skip! Skip!
mousou darake de
妄想だらけで
Full of crazy ideas!
dasshu dasshu
ダッシュダッシュ
Dash! Dash!
chikoku wa genjitsu sokka sokka
遅刻は現実 そっかそっか
Being late has become reality, I see, I see
sekai wa kyou mo todokoori naku janjan mawaruyo
世界は今日も 滞りなくじゃんじゃんまわるよ
The world today is also filled with love, climbing non-stop
ii kanji de (hai)
いい感じで(ハイ)
It feels great
hashire hashire
はしれはしれ
Run! Run!
otome otome
オトメオトメ
Girl! Girl!
GO! or GO!
Go or Go
itsudatte
いつだって
As always,
kyou ga numbah one saikou tte sakende ikiteyaru
今日がNo.1 最高って叫んで生きてやる
Shout out, "Today is number one!" "Today's the best!"
hashire hashire
はしれはしれ
Run! Run!
otome otome
オトメオトメ
Girl! Girl!
GO! & GO!
Go & Go
tatoeba hito tobi taimumashin de
例えばひとッ飛びタイムマシーンで
For example, a one-leap time machine.
sore tte saikou (saiko desu—)
それって最高(さいこですー)
That's the greatest!
Ah!
This week's episode gave me so much eye candy, I got all excited!
Ayumu, let's ignore this idiot and move on to the preview.
Yup!
Next time, on Hoshizora e Kakaru Hashi, episode 9:
Wasps are Diurnal.
Next time
Wasps are Diurnal
Also, Ayumu should have worn a micro-bikini school swimsuit.
That would have been perfect!
That isn't something a guy would wear.
Then it's fine if it's something guys wear?
Well, that's...
Okay, Ayumu!
Next episode, let's try wearing a loincloth!
Okay!
"Okay", not!